

avnip@gmail.com

25, green avanue, surat, 456895, india

1234567890

Profile

Broad-based Human Resources experience spanning from strategic Human Resources to managing Talent Acquisition, Talent Engagement, Employer Branding, HR Digitization, Learning & Development, Organization Culture, People Transformation, Project & Change Management. bgjhdgjdbgjbdjbgjbhdj dig i

ghdfjghjdghjdfhgjhdfgjhdfjkghjkdfhgjkdfhgjhdfjghfdjhgjkdfhgjkhfdgjhhdfjghdjfhg jfdhgjhdfgjkhfdkjghdkfjghdjkfhgkjfghjkdfhgjkhfdighrihfhgiihidfhgkjdfhgkjhdfkjh gkjdhfgkjhdfkjghkjdfhgjkhdfkjghkjdhfgkjhdfjkghkjdfjkdhgjkdhdjkhdkfjhgkjdfhgkj dhgkdfhgkhdfkghdihghkidfhgkdhfkghdfk

Employment History

Founder, CEO At GoEvals Solutions Private Ltd., Mumbai, India, April 2019 - Present, Surat

Jan, 2021 - Present

 GoEvals is an analysis-driven, Al-enabled, digital tools platform. Our mission is to be the most impactful technology investment for the people management practice of our clients.

Laravel, , Navsari

Jan, 2021 - Nov, 2021

 In order to ensure that your professional resume is supporting your career goals, gather a few sample job descriptions that describe the type of position you're interested in and qualified for. Then, compare the skills and qualifications on your resume with the desired qualifications in the sample job descriptions.

,

•

.

Education

, Strategy In International Business, Indian Institute Of Foreign Trade, Mumbai Jan, 2021 - Present

One of the most important documents you'll need to update or create
for this process is your professional resume. A great resume is written
with a specific job goal in mind. It should be tailored for each job
application by showcasing your most valuable and relevant skills in a
way that positions you as an ideal candidate for the job you want.

Ssc, Gkv, Surat

Jan, 2021 - Present

 One of the most important documents you'll need to update or create for this process is your professional resume. A great resume is written with a specific job goal in mind. It should be tailored for each job

Details

25, green avanue surat 456895 india 1234567890 avni

Date/Place of Birth

20/12/1996

Surat

Links

twitter linked in

Skills

Laravel

• • • • • •

Jquery

Language

Hindi

■ ■ ■ I English

Hobbies

In order to ensure that your professional resume is supporting your career goals, gather a few sample job descriptions that describe the type of position you're interested in and qualified for. Then, compare the skills and qualifications on your resume with the desired qualifications in the sample job descriptions.

application by showcasing your most valuable and relevant skills in a way that positions you as an ideal candidate for the job you want.

, , -

•

Courses

Php, Sassy

Jan, 2021 - Nov, 2021

Laravel, Sassyinfotech

Jan, 2021 - Present

Html, Sassy

Jan, 2021 - Present

Extra-Curricular Activity

Html , Sassy , California

Jan, 2021 - Nov, 2021

• dhfughudfhg udfgudfhudfu du ghudrghurhdgudurghdfu

Dance,,

Jan, 2021 - Present

•

Dance,, Surat

Jan, 2021 -

 In order to ensure that your professional resume is supporting your career goals, gather a few sample job descriptions that describe the type of position you're interested in and qualified for. Then, compare the skills and qualifications on your resume with the desired qualifications in the sample job descriptions.

Internships

Html,,

Feb, 2021 - Aug, 2021

•

Css, Sassy, Surat

Jan, 2021 -

 In order to ensure that your professional resume is supporting your career goals, gather a few sample job descriptions that describe the type of position you're interested in and qualified for. Then, compare the skills and qualifications on your resume with the desired qualifications in the sample job descriptions.

, ,

•

Custom

Php, Surat

Jan, 2021 - Present

• hdfghdrjh gud huhdu hdgduhgudghu ud hgudjfgjh jdgh djjg

Laravel,

Jan, 2021 - Jul, 2021

•

Reference

 $\mbox{\ensuremath{I'}\xspace}\mbox{\ensuremath{d}}\xspace$ like to hide references and make them available only upon request